can now let's go ahead and look at one of the AWS services in the area of computer vision
and it's called as Amazon Recognition. So Amazon Recognition provides
computer vision capabilities to extract information and insights from images and videos.
So earlier we discussed one of the most common use cases for computer vision is content
moderation to detect in the appropriate content. Now let's see how Amazon Recognition enables
this capability. So Amazon Recognition is a managed service which can automatically detect
in appropriate content in an image. So you have the Amazon Recognition service.
Now let's say you upload an image and then Amazon Recognition service is going to be triggered
and then it can classify the content as regular content or it can blur or delete the content
if it identifies the image as inappropriate content. So the other use case where you can use
Amazon Recognition is to onboard new customers where you can verify the identity online using Amazon
Recognition. Then you could also use Amazon Recognition for streaming media analysis where
Amazon Recognition can help analyze and tag videos of celebrities and other people and this
video stream can be live or it can be recorded videos. Now let's go ahead and go to this
Amazon Recognition Service and see what other capabilities it offers.